Hotel Acuna, please.
請到Acuna旅店.
-What's his name? -Eduardo Acuna. He's the big boss.
-他叫什么名字？ -Eduardo Acuna. 他是大老板.
-Here's his office. -Oh, thanks.
-這里是他的辦公室 -哦，謝謝
Oh, boy.
Oh, 侍童過來
l'll get you later. Thanks.
晚一點再給你小費。謝謝
l absolutely, positively cannot interrupt Mr. Acuna.
（電話）我是絕對不能打擾Acuna先生的.
He is busy.
他在忙.
Sorry, those are my orders.
抱歉，那些是我接到的命令.
Please don't blame me.
請別責備我
-When he's free, l'd like to see him. -l ask myself the same question.
-等他有空的時候，我想見他. -我不停地問自己一個同樣的問題.
Why see Mr. Acuna when there are so many pleasant people they could see?
為什么所有的人都要見Acuna先生 而放著那么多和善的人不去見？
Tell him Robert Davis of New York is here.
告訴他紐約的Robert Davis在這兒。
-Robert Davis. -Yes?
-Robert Davis. -什么事?
Mr. Robert Davis of New York to see you, Mr. Acuna.
Acuna先生，紐約來的Mr. Robert Davis 想要見你。
I never heard of him. Tell him to go away.
我從來沒有聽過這個人，叫他走。
Well, l must say, l'm used to more cordiality than that.
Well, l must say, l'm used to more cordiality than that. 誒，我必須說我過去可比那誠實多了。
He's making a big mistake.
他可犯了一個大錯.
Mr. Davis, you impress me. What did you want to see him about?
Davis先生, 你真讓人印象深刻. 你是為什么事情要見他？
That.
那個.
What?
什么?
-l only asked you a civil question. -And l answered you.
-我剛剛問了一個很禮貌的問題. -我也回答了你.
-You don't mind if l wait? -No, but it won't do you any good.
-你不介意我在這里等吧? -不，但是你要知道這樣對你并沒有什么好處.
That's very nice. The wedding dress and the lingerie, l approve.
這套禮服和襯衣真美，我很滿意。
You may go, and thank you.
你可以走了，謝謝
Well, darling, what's been going on here?
哦親愛的,這里在干什么呢
Eduardo had a slight disagreement with Delfina about Julia's trousseau...
Eduardo 對于Julia的嫁妝稍有些不滿
...so now he's picking out one himself.
...所以現在他親自來挑選
lt's my invariable rule to distrust women's taste in clothes.
不信任女人對于服裝的品位是我一貫的作風。
That's why he asked me to come by.
那就是為什么他叫我也一起來。
First time l heard of a father selecting a trousseau.
我第一次聽說一個父親來挑選女兒的嫁妝。
You know as well as l do that women dress for one another, not for men.
你跟我都知道女人穿衣服不是為了男人，而是另一個人。
Delfina's mother put her in fluff when l married her.
Delfina的媽媽嫁給我的時候 把她自己放在一堆絨毛里面。
She's been in fluff ever since. Does your son like fluff?
從那時到現在她一直都鐘愛毛茸茸的 裝飾你的兒子喜歡毛茸茸的東西嗎？
My dear, for the first few weeks, he won't know what Julia's wearing.
我親愛的，最開始的几個星期 他不會知道Julia穿的是什么。
-Will your wife forgive you for this? -Forgive me? l expect to be thanked.
-你的妻子會原諒你自己決定Julia的禮服嗎？ -原諒我？她會感謝我的。
-And thank you, Maria, for coming. -That's all right. Goodbye, Eduardo.
-謝謝你Maria，謝謝你陪我來。 -沒問題，再見。
-Who are you, the florist? -Do l look like a florist?
-你是誰，園丁？ -我看起來像個園丁么？
How do l know what a florist looks like? Who are you?
我怎么知道園丁長什么樣子，你是誰？
Xavier Cugat, remember me?
Xavier Cugat，記得我么？
Didn't l bring you down here from New York for something?
我把你從紐約帶來是為了什么？
My orchestra has packed your Sky Room for the past two weeks.
我的樂隊已經在你的天空房間待了兩周了。
That is something!
那就是你說的事情！
l never go to the Sky Room. My cover charge is too high.
我從來沒有去過天空房間 我要管的東西太多了。
Of course! You're to play at my daughter's wedding tomorrow.
對了，明天你們將在我女兒的婚宴上演奏。
Very well.
正是。
Play this softly and remotely, as though you were not there.
.要輕柔的演奏這個曲子 就像你們人不在這兒。
Mr. Acuna, you can forget my name, stay away from the Sky Room...
你可以不記得我的名字，不去看天空房間，
...underpay me, but you cannot dictate how my orchestra should play.
扣我工錢，但是你不能指揮我的樂隊怎么演奏。
You play this softly.
記得溫柔的彈奏！
How l wish l was back at the Waldorf.
我真希望能回到Waldorf。
-Bob Davis! -Cugie!
-Bob Davis! -Cugie!
What are you doing here?
你怎么會出現在這里？
l just came down for a holiday. l didn't know you were here.
我是來度假的。我不知道你也在這里。
A holiday? You didn't know there was a racetrack here?
度假？別說你不知道這里有一場賽馬。
-Well, yes, and-- -And now you're broke again?
-其實也是，而且。。。 -而且你又輸了？
Yep, l gotta put these feet back to work for a while.
是啊，我必須靠我的雙腳工作一陣子了。
But, gee, l like it here. You know, the people, the city, the horses.
但是上帝啊，我喜歡這兒 這兒的人，這個城市，還有馬。
But this fellow, Acuna, he's tough. He won't see me.
那是Acuna這家伙，他是個壞蛋。 他不肯見我。
Acuna won't see him?
Acuna不肯見他？
Why, in New York, he won't see Acuna.
為什么？在紐約Acuna想見他都見不到。
This, Fernando, is the greatest man in the world.
他，Fernando是這個世界上最偉大的舞者。
Tell Acuna that Mr. Davis will give him just two minutes of his time.
告訴Acuna Davis先生只會給他兩分鐘的時間。
Oh, no. You tell him.
.哦，不，你自己去告訴他。
Yes, Mr. Acuna?
有什么事情，Acuna先生？
Remind me to give Cugat back to the Waldorf. He annoys me.
記得提醒我把Cugat送去Waldorf，他煩死人了。
Very funny man. He kills me.
多幽默的人啊。 他害死我了。
You know, actually l have a great deal of influence with Acuna. What's that?
你知道，其實我對Acuna有很大的影響力。怎么？
l didn't say a thing. Just minding my own business.
我什么也沒有說。 我只是坐在這里干自己的事情。
Come along. l've a show to do. While we play, we'll think of something.
跟我走，我還有一場表演。 到時候我們談談。
Terrific! l've made up my mind. We'll work together again!
太棒了！我有一個主意，我們要再一次合作。
-With you, we'll be better than terrific. -l don't like Acuna's attitude.
-.跟你一起表演，我們會更棒的。 -我不喜歡Acuna的態度。
-l'm going to change it right now. -No, l have a better way.
-我現在就去辭退了他那的工作。 -等等，我有個更好的主意。
l'm playing at his daughter's wedding. You will sing, you will dance.
我將在她女兒的婚宴上表演。 到時候你來唱歌和跳舞。
You will be sensational! Acuna will come to you on his knees.
你將會打動所有人的心。 Acuna會拜倒在你的膝下。
lt's almost time, Julia.
時間快到了，Julia.
Here's your something old, sis, and a new coin for your something new.
這是你的舊東西，姐姐，這是一個嶄新的硬幣。
Thanks, Lita.
謝謝你，Lita。
And Mama's handkerchief for something borrowed.
還有媽媽的手帕，是借來的東西。
Here's something blue, Julia
這是藍色的東西，Julia。
The bridegroom's supposed to sleep on it, or something.
新郎要睡在上面。
l suppose l should put the coin in my shoe.
我想我應該把硬幣放在鞋子里。
You'll be the next bride in the family, Maria.
你將是這個家里的第二個新娘，Maria。
-Oh, no. Not me. -Oh, but you have to be.
-不，不是我。 -你必須是。
Papa made it very clear that we can't get married until after you do.
爸爸很明確地說了，我們要在你之后才能結婚。
He says it's our family tradition that the girls be disposed of...
他說這是我們家的傳統，所有的女兒們必須按
...one, two, three, four.
從大到小的順序嫁出去
And you'll be the oldest now.
現在你就是最年長的了。
Papa will get over that silly tradition.
爸爸會在這種愚蠢的傳統上妥協的
No, he won't. Papa never gets over anything.
不，他不會的。 爸爸從來不會妥協。
You don't expect to marry those two tennis-playing Romeos, do you?
你們兩個不是想要嫁給那兩個打網球的羅密歐吧？
But we love Tony and Roddy passionately.
可是我們是那么的愛Tony和Roddy。
They've even given us their signet rings, see?
他們甚至給了我們他們的戒指，瞧？
Why, you're babies.
你們真天真。
You just don't know what it's like to be so much in love that you cry all night.
你只是不知道因為深愛某人而整夜哭泣的感覺。
You're right there.
沒錯。
lt's all right for you to talk. You turn men down by the dozens.
你說起來輕松。 你拒絕了那么多的追求者。
You've got an ice cube for a heart.
你有一顆冰冷的心。
-Unaccustomed as l am to getting a-- -There's something wrong with Maria.
-我真不習慣介入。。 -爸爸，Maria有問題。
-She says she'll never get married. -l did not say that.
-她說她不打算嫁人。 -我可沒有那么說。
You know, Papa, l think you'd better put a cooling system in their room.
你知道，爸爸，我想你最好給這個房間降降溫。
Now, you leave Maria to me. Don't worry, she's next...
現在，我來解決Maria的問題。 別擔心，她是下一個結婚的。
...and then will come your turn, and then yours.
然后就是你 最后是你。
-Do we have to wait for Maria? -Yes.
-我們必須得等Maria結婚么？ -當然。
And this is a fine way to act on your sister's wedding day.
別忘記了今天是你們姐姐的婚禮。
Now, run along and fix your pretty faces.
現在你們去整一下妝，把自己打扮得漂漂亮亮的。
Getting nervous, dear? We're going to miss you.
緊張么？親愛的。 我們會想你的。
Has Mama forgiven you yet for picking out my trousseau?
媽媽原諒你給我挑選禮服這件事情了么？
l don't know. Her door was locked.
我不知道，她把自己鎖在房里。
She broke down and confessed that she liked my dress.
她妥協了，并且公開說她喜歡你給我挑的禮服。
These skirmishes l have with your mother are not typical of married life.
這只是我們婚姻生活中的一場小沖突 比起其它的不算什么。
-Aren't they, Father? -No, they're just typical of me.
-是么？爸爸 -是，這只是我的特征。
-l'm very difficult to live with. -No, you're not, darling.
-我很難相處的。 -你不是的，親愛的。
You're really just a little boy, and l love you.
你只是一個小男孩兒。 我愛你。
And l love you too, darling.
我也愛你，親愛的。
Will you hook me, Eduardo?
能幫我扣一下么？
Delfina, don't you think it's about time you learned to dress yourself?
Delfina,你不覺得是時候學習自己穿衣服么？
lt's so hard for me to believe l'm old enough to have a married daughter.
真叫人難以相信我已經老到有一個嫁人的女兒了。
lt doesn't put any strain on me.
這對我沒有一丁點兒的壓力。
Julia. Where are the rest of my girls?
Julia. 剩下那几個女兒在哪兒呢？
Oh, Maria! Lita! Cecy!
Oh, Maria! Lita! Cecy!
-Coming, Mother. -Coming, Mama!
-來了，媽媽。 -就來，媽媽。
l want to see you all in a row.
我想看你們站成一排。
Oh! l'm going to cry tonight.
Oh!我今晚上肯定要哭了。
You'd better start now. lt's getting late. Do you want some last-minute advice?
你最好現在就開始，現在已經很晚了。 你最后還有什么要求么？
Just don't act too intelligent on your honeymoon.
記住可別在度蜜月的時候表現得太聰明。
l made that mistake with your father.
我跟你爸爸結婚的時候就犯了這個錯誤。
That reminds me. Tell me something clever to say after the wedding.
對了，告訴我一些應對的話 好在婚禮結束以后說。
Oh, dear, l'm so happy.
哦，親愛的，我真是太高興了。
Hurry, girls. Now remember, keep in step.
快點，姑娘們。 記住，保持步伐。
l am going to cry. l'm going to cry right now.
我快要哭了。 我馬上就要哭了。
He didn't even look around.
他看都沒看一眼。
Have your son pass the word. l have three more where Julia came from.
你們的兒子通過口令了么？ 我這兒有三個 Julia哪里來 的答案。
-You two ask Papa now. -While he's laughing.
-你們兩個現在就跟爸爸說。 -瞧他在笑呢。
Come on.
走。
-Mr. Acuna. -Yes?
-Mr. Acuna. -什么事？
We've been going with your daughters Cecy and Lita for two years now and--
我們跟你的兩個女兒Cecy和Lita在一起兩年了。。。
What do you want, a pension?
你們要什么呢？養老金？
-All right, who's going to be next? -l am.
-好了，姑娘們，誰是下一個？ -我
-Maria has to catch it. -Yes.
-必須保証Maria拿到捧花。 -對。
But l don't want it.
但是我不需要。
-Here's a volunteer groom. -Let's have a double wedding.
-這里有一個自愿的新郎。 -我們來個雙喜臨門。
-l'm between engagements. -Here l am.
-我沒有婚約 -我。
How about me?
我怎樣？
Oh, you're all much too kind.
哦，你們實在是太善良了。
Papa! Papa! Did you see Maria? She froze those boys.
爸爸！爸爸！你看見Maria的態度了么？ 她拒絕了那些男兒。
Papa, you've just got to do something about her.
爸爸，你必須跟她談談了。
Pardon me, could you please tell me where l could find Mr. Acuna?
打擾一下，你可以告訴我 什么地方可以找到Acuna先生么？
He went inside.
他進去了。
On second thought, l guess old el groucho can wait.
想一想，這個老家伙還可以等等。
Don't these overdone weddings bore you to death? They kill me.
你不覺得這些婚宴無聊死了么？ 我都快要窒息了。
l say if two people want to get married, let them.
我說要是兩個人想要結婚，讓他們結就是了。
They don't have to go through a shindig like this. lt's murder.
他們不需要像這樣狂歡一氣。這簡直是謀殺。
Oh, well, l'll admit my attempt at conversation wasn't so hot.
恩，我必須承認我試圖使談話不那么緊湊。
Shall l try again?
你不覺得么？
lt's a nice day, isn't it?
今天天氣真好，不是么？
The air's nice.
空氣很新鮮。
And there seems to be an abundance of it.
而且很充足。
Say, look, would you mind very much if l tear myself away from you?
你看，你不會介意我現在飛奔的逃開吧。
No.
請便。
But you don't understand.
但是你不明白，爸爸。
Now, let's hear no more about Maria. Run along, girls.
現在我們不再談Maria。自己去玩吧，姑娘們。
May l see you a moment, please? lt's very important to both of us.
我可以跟你談談么？ 這對我們雙方都很重要。
l'm Robert Davis. l came here to dance and--
我是Robert Davis 我是來這兒跳舞和。。。
Hello.
你好。
Now, what is there about that girl that made you go--?
你為什么對那個姑娘--
She's beautiful.
她很美。
She's beautiful, all right.
沒錯，她很美。
But she has a personality like the inside of a refrigerator.
但是她的性格卻很冰冷。
ln addition to which, she is my daughter.
我要提醒你，她是我的女兒。
She is? She is?!
當然。她？
She is. Now, what was it you wanted of me?
她是。現在你談談你想要什么？
Just your permission to go out and hang myself.
只是請你允許我出去吊死我自己。
Fernando.
Fernando.
Fernando!
Fernando!
What?
什么？
Were you sleeping again?
你又在睡覺么？
Tell me, my dear Fernando, why do I put up with you?
告訴我,親愛的Fernando， 為什么我會容忍你這種人。
l don't know, Mr. Acuna...
我也不知道Mr. Acuna...
...unless it's because l'm your third cousin on your wife's side.
...至少我是你夫人那邊第三個侄子。
Ah, yes. Did you get Mrs. Castro?
啊，沒錯。你聯系了Mrs. Castro么？
Mrs. Castro is on her way here.
Mrs. Castro正在往這兒來。
All right.
太好了。
Now go back to sleep, Fernando.
繼續睡吧，Fernando。
I dare you to!
我敢說你一定會睡的！
-Hi, Fernando. -Good morning, Mr. Davis.
-你好Fernando. -早啊，Mr. Davis。
lt's good to hear the voice of a human being again. Sit down?
總算又聽到像人類一般的聲音了。 請坐
No, thanks. l'd like to see Mr. Acuna if he's not busy.
不了，謝謝。如果他不忙得話我想見Mr. Acuna。
This morning he's nervous. He probably won't see you.
他今天早上很神經。 可能不會見你。
-How'd you make out? -Oh, fine.
-進展得怎么樣？ -還好。
l opened my mouth too wide and kept it open too long.
我說了不該說的話，還說得挺多的。
l want to apologize to the old boy.
我想向那個老小孩兒道個歉。
Mr. Robert Davis wants to see you, Mr. Acuna.
Robert Davis先生想要見您，Mr. Acuna。
I don't like Mr. Robert Davis. I don't want to see him.
我不喜歡他，我不想見他。
Advise him to go back to New York and don't be subtle.
叫他最好回紐約并且別再那么陰險。
Throw him out!
把他扔出去！
But look, Mr. Acuna, l just....
但是你看，Mr. Acuna，我只是想
This is the first time anything like this has ever happened to me.
這可是我第一次受到這樣的待遇。
Oh, lady.
女士.
Better not to go in there. Nervous.
最好別進去，這人神經質。
-Good morning, Maria. -Eduardo.
-早啊，Maria， -Eduardo.
l'm a worried man. Maria, besides having the same name...
有些事情讓我悶悶不樂。Maria。 除了一個相同的名字
...you and my Maria have a lot in common, haven't you?
你跟我女兒Maria還有很多東西很像，不是么？
Well, l'm her godmother, we should have.
我是教母呀 這是當然的。
Would you say she has a personality like the inside of a refrigerator?
你會說她是的性格像從冰箱里面拿出來的一樣么？
l certainly would not.
我當然不會。
But she freezes men to death. She turns on that sophistication--
但是她對男人一點都不感興趣。 她變得很難纏--
Sophistication, fiddlesticks!
難纏？胡說！
Maria's as old-fashioned as a hoop skirt.
就像裙箍一樣守舊。
Ridiculous! l know my own daughter.
荒謬，我知道我自己的女兒。
You think you know your own daughter.
你以為你明白你的女兒。
l know there's something wrong.
我知道她肯定有什么問題。
She hasn't fallen in love since she was 1 5...
從她15歲對白馬王子滿懷憧憬開始
...when she got starry-eyed about that silly knight on a white horse.
她就一直沒有戀愛過。
-Lochinvar? -Yes.
-Lochinvar? -Yes.是的。
You'd think she'd have outgrown that tin hero by now.
你可以想象她已經過了崇拜的年齡。
She's probably waiting for a myth to come to life.
她可能在等某個人如神話一般的走到她的面前。
Oh, nonsense! Will you stop thinking of Maria as a child? She's a woman.
胡說。你就不能把她當成一個女人而不再是女兒么？
l know women. They all fall in love with an illusion. l'll get her over that.
我懂女人。女人都愛幻想。我要她結束幻想。
Will you leave Maria alone and stop worrying?
你不能停止擔心讓她自己處理。
Someday, a man will come along who will stir her imagination.
總有一天，會有一個男人走進她的心里。
How?
怎樣？
By doing something more romantic than the others.
他會做一些比其他人更浪漫的事情來打動她。
Such as?
例如說？
Well, perhaps by sending her flowers from an ''unknown admirer''...
可能是以“無名的仰慕者”的名義給她送花。
...intriguing her with just the right kind of note.
...以剛好可以吸引她的方式迷倒她。
Fernando! Get the two most beautiful orchids you can find.
Fernando!去給我找最美麗的紫蘭花。
Bring them here for a note to be attached.
把它們帶過來另外附加一張便條。
Eduardo, don't you meddle with this.
Eduardo你別用這些瞎搗亂。
lf l don't do something, she'll get hurt.
如果我不做些什么的話， 她會傷心的。
l won't stand by and let her waste the best years of her life chasing knights.
我也不會眼睜睜的看著她白白浪費 她一生中最美的時光在白馬王子的身上。
Have you gone crazy? You can't manufacture romance.
你瘋了么？ 你不能制造浪漫。
l'll create an unknown admirer and see what happens.
我會創造一個無名的仰慕者，看看會發生什么事情
l'll use my left hand to disguise my writing. Clever?
我會用左手寫讓她看不出來，聰明吧？
You think you have the answer for everything.
你以為你可以控制所有的事情。
What if she falls in love with your imaginary lover?
如果她愛上了你捏造出來的那個男人怎么辦？
Don't worry. lf the orchids and notes intrigue her...
別擔心，假如那些蘭花和便條可以吸引她。。。
...l'll furnish the young man myself. She'll never know the difference.
...我會親自為她找一個年輕人 她永遠也會不知道。
Dearly beloved....
兩個人深深的相愛。
Eduardo, l'm warning you.
我可警告過你。
-Papa! Hello, Aunt Maria. -Hello.
-爸爸！你好，Maria阿姨。 -你好。
What are you doing here?
你們來有什么事呢？
Must l have an invitation to my own home for tea?
我不能回自己的家享受一杯茶么？
-ls that you, Eduardo? -Yes, yes.
-是你么？Eduardo? -是的。
What on earth are you doing here?
你們在這兒做什么呢？
You'd think my only privilege in this house was paying the bills.
你該不是想我在這個房子中 唯一的權力是付每月的賬單吧。
Aunt Maria, it's good to see you.
Maria阿姨，真高興見到你。
-Wasn't that the doorbell? -Expecting somebody, Papa?
-門鈴響了么？ -你在期待某人么？爸爸
No, why should l be expecting somebody? Sit down, Maria.
不，為什么我要期待某人？請坐，Maria。
Thank you.
謝謝。
l'm really upset with your son, Maria...
Maria我對你的兒子真感到失望
...and with your daughter Julia, Eduardo!
還有你的女兒Julia,Eduardo！
l went to the hotel where they're honeymooning.
我去過他們蜜月的旅店。
-What for? ln the name of all-- -Don't speak when l'm interrupting.
-為什么？ -別打斷我說話。
To see if there was anything l could do for them.
我去看看有什么要我幫忙的。
As if there would be.
就像真的會有一樣。
l thought they'd want to discuss what they intend to do on their honeymoon.
我原以為他們會討論蜜月怎么過。
But they sent down word they weren't in.
但是他們留下字條說他們沒有去那兒。
Perhaps they weren't, Delfina.
隨他們吧，Delfina。
At the same time, they also sent down for a bottle of champagne.
同時，他們也留下了一瓶香檳。
-l felt like-- -Wasn't that the doorbell?
---我感覺就像是。。 -是門鈴響么？
Something's wrong with Papa. He's always hearing bells.
爸爸今天真奇怪。 他總是聽到門鈴響。
Well, well, well! Orchids.
蘭花。
Shame on Tony. He should save his money.
Tony真是的，他應該剩下這筆錢的。
-How do you know they're not for me? -Bring me the flowers, Cecy.
-你怎么知道不是我的？ -把那些花給我看看，Cecy。
Why, there's a card inside.
別爭了，里面有張卡片。
Nobody ever sends me flowers.
可從來沒有人給我送過花。
After a woman gets married...
一個女人出嫁后
...her husband decides she can't smell anymore.
她的丈夫覺得她失去了嗅覺。
Now, don't get that martyred look. They're for Maria.
哦，別一臉受了折磨的樣子。 這是給Maria的。
-For Maria? -Why, they-- They are for Maria.
-給Maria的？ -怎么會？他們真是給Maria的
Well, somebody's just trying to be funny.
哦，一定是某人開的玩笑吧。
''Dearly beloved, l send you orchids--''
我深愛的人，送上紫蘭花”
-Let Maria read her own card. -Go ahead, Mama.
-讓Maria自己讀。 -沒關系，媽媽。
lt probably ends up with a joke.
可能是玩笑結尾也說不定。
''--because my heart is no longer mine, now that l have seen you.
''--因為我的心已經不再屬于我 自從我見到你的那一刻開始”
Be kind to these orchids.
請善待這些蘭花。
lt is not their fault that they can never be as lovely as you.''
永遠不能像你一樣可愛并不是他們的錯。
Why, it brought tears to my eyes.
天哪，我都要感動得流淚了。
That note was written by a man with a sensitive soul.
那張便條一定是某個心思細膩的男人寫的。
lt sounded pretty silly to me.
這對我來說確實很愚蠢的。
A charming man sends you the most beautiful note ever written...
一個這么迷人的男人送給你最動人的語句
...and you say it sounds silly?
...而你卻說很愚蠢？
''Your unknown suitor.'' And l don't think much of his handwriting.
你無名的仰慕者”。而且我也不喜歡他的字體。
Well, perhaps he's left-handed.
恩，可能他是左撇子也說不定。
How does this card strike you, Aunt Maria?
你覺得這張卡片怎么樣？Maria阿姨。
lf it had been sent to me and l didn't know who'd written it...
如果這是給我的，如果我不知道這是誰寫的。。。
-...l should think it was pretty silly. -Aunt Maria's right.
-...我一定會覺得這很滑稽。 -Maria阿姨是對的。
Whoever he is, he'll have to do better than that.
不管他是誰，他可要努力了。
Let me see the card, Maria, please.
讓我看看那張卡片，Maria，求你了。
-What are you two whispering about? -Well, l--
-你們兩個在嘀咕什么呢？ --恩，我--
l was saying that if that note didn't warm Maria's heart...
我剛剛在說如果那張卡片不能溫暖Maria的心。。。
...the next one, l believe, may well start a flame within her.
下一次，我相信會點燃她心中的火焰。
Why, Eduardo, you remind me of our courting days.
哦，Eduardo，你讓我記起 我們起我們戀愛的日子。
He was always telling me how l lit a flame in him.
他常常說我怎樣點燃他心中的熱情。
Sometimes l wonder if it hasn't gone out.
有時我會想它是熄滅了呢？
l'll have you know that l'm twice the man l was.
我會讓你知道現在加倍愛你了。
l would settle for half the man you were, dear.
如果有以前的一半我就滿足了。
Here are the love lyrics you wanted.
.這是你要的情詩。
The love songs and the great love letters of Napoleon.
情歌和拿破侖著名的情書。
Just put them down and get out.
放在那里然后出去。
Sorry!
對不起。
Right on time, 5:00.
真准時，5點鐘。
You know, Louise, l'm beginning to wonder what he's like.
你知道，Louise，我開始想知道他長什么樣子了。
She's in love at last.
她終于動心了。
l'm going to wear Tony's ring where everybody can see it.
我要帶上Tony送的戒指讓所有的人都能看到。
Now we can be secretly engaged and tell everybody.
我們可以秘密的籌備了，然后再告訴大家。
-No orchids for almost a week. -Sunk again.
-.快一周沒有受到蘭花了。 -又失敗了。
l guess we'd better put our rings back.
我猜我們要把戒指收起來了。
Hello.
你好。
Oh, hello, Papa. When did you get back in town?
你好，爸爸。 你什么時候從城中回來的？
Just now. How's everything at home?
剛剛才到。家里一切還好吧。
Oh, we're all right, but Maria's in the dumps.
我們都好。只有Maria有些壓抑。
Maria, in the dumps? Why?
Maria很壓抑？為什么？
She hasn't received orchids all week.
她整周都沒有收到蘭花。
No orchids all week? How stupid of me!
一周都沒有收到蘭花？ 我真笨！
l mean, tell her, of course, that no one's been making a fool of her.
不是，我是說，告訴她，當然，別人不是在耍她。
No, don't tell her anything.
別，還是別什么也別告訴她。
Well, how does she know the orchid sender didn't get sick?
她怎么知道那個送蘭花的人有沒有生病？
Well, say hello to your mother. See you soon. Goodbye.
恩，跟你們的母親問好。 再見。
Dearly beloved...
我深愛的人。。。
...although l have been desperately ill...
...雖然我病的神志不清
...in my delirium, they....
...在我昏迷的時候
ln my delirium, they told me l asked only for you.
在我昏迷的時候，他們告訴我 我呼喊的只有你的名字。
Have you got my number? 3 790.
你有我的號碼么？ 3 790.
This time, he's shaving.
他正在刮胡子。
No, don't bring a lottery ticket in here.
不，別帶一張彩卷到這兒來。
l can escape to the lobby for a moment.
我可以溜到會議室去。
-l'll see you there. Right now. -Did you give him my message?
-那里見。馬上。 -你給他我留的信息了么？
Yes, and he said to have you arrested for trespassing if you came in again.
給了，但是他說如果你再來 就要告你非法入侵，要拘留你。
Mr. Davis, give up. He'll never see you.
先生放棄吧，他不會見你的。
Fernando. Send a bellboy in here immediately.
馬上給我找個送貨的來。
Mr. Acuna?
Mr. Acuna?
There's money and a note on my desk.
錢和便條在我的桌上。
Take them, buy two magnificent orchids...
拿著它們，買兩束高貴的蘭花。。
...attach the note, then take the flowers to my home. ls that clear?
...配上便條，送到我家里，明白么？
Yes, sir. But first, could l see--?
明白，先生。但是我可以。。
Hurry it up! This is an emergency. And bring back the change.
馬上！這很緊急。 記得把零錢帶回來。
Yes, sir.
知道了，先生。
l'll be back.
我會回來的。
''Dearly beloved, dearly beloved...
我深愛的人，我深愛的人
...dearly beloved, dearly beloved.''
我深愛的人我深愛的人
-l wouldn't take it so hard. -l'm not taking anything hard.
-別這么激動。 -我沒有為任何事情激動。
Beware of note writers who haven't the courage to court you face to face.
你要知道這個送花的人 沒有勇氣當面向你式愛。
Even my clock's slow.
連我的鐘都慢。
No, it isn't. Look, dear. Look.
沒有，它沒有慢。親愛的，瞧。
''For Miss Maria Acuna.'' Thank you, sir.
給Maria小姐的，謝謝你先生。
Thank you with all my heart and soul.
我全心全意地謝謝你。
You're an angel.
你就是一個天使。
Hoist the anchor, Cecy, we're in again.
Cecy,起起落落，Cecy,我們又有戲了。
You know, l think l've seen him before.
你知道么？我覺得我以前見過他。
Louise, would you be a darling and pick up the pieces of notes l tore up?
可以請你幫我把剛剛 那些撕碎的便條撿起來么？
Yes, yes.
當然。
''Dearly beloved....''
我深愛的人。。。
Jumping blue blazes!
要那種跳躍的藍色火焰的！
Can't you even order a teapot for that hotel without calling me?
你就不能離開我自己從酒店訂購一個茶壺么？
Why do l put up with it? All right, all right.
為什么我要容忍你。 好的，好的。
Maybe l can fly up next week.
可能我下一周就受不了你了
ln the meanwhile, start looking for another profession.
到那時你要開始找另一份工作了。
One that won't require the use of that addled fraction of a brain of yours.
一分不需要用你那個笨腦袋的工作。
Mr. Acuna, here's your change.
Mr.Acuna，這是你的零錢。
Two pesos, 50 centavos.
兩比索五十分。
-What are you doing here? -l delivered the orchids for you...
-你怎么會在這里？ -我剛給你送過蘭花
-...now you're going-- -You delivered the orchids?
-...現在你要。。。 -是你送的那些蘭花？
l'm not gonna try to figure out how you substituted yourself for a bellboy.
我不想知道你怎么代替的那個送花人。
Mr. Acuna, l've been trying for days to dance for you.
Mr.Acuna，這些天來我一直 希望能夠給你跳一場舞。
You're the only man who's ever refused to see my work, and l resent it.
從來沒有人拒絕我的舞蹈 除了你。對此我很憤怒。
Get out of my office!
從我的辦公室滾出去！
Now, look, this is a matter of pride with me. l don't like to dance, see?
這是我自尊心的問題 你知道么？我并不喜歡跳舞。
l came down here to get away from it.
事實上，我跑到這里來就是為了躲避跳舞。
Shall l have you thrown out?
你要我找人扔你出去么？
You can't talk that way to me. Honest, l'm an important guy.
你不能那種口氣跟我說話 老實說，我可是一個很重要的人物。
Now, you're gonna see me dance and like it.
現在你要看我跳舞，并且馬上喜歡上它。
Oh, no, l'm not.
不，我才不要。
Oh, yes, you are. Take it, boys. One, two.
你會的。看著，伙計們，一二。
-Well? -Excellent. Beautiful.
-怎樣？ -完美，華麗。
But l don't want it. Mr. Davis...
但是我不需要。 Mr. Davis...
...you do something to me that results in the most fascinating dislike ever.
...你對我做的事情導致我無比的厭惡。
-May l make an observation? -You may make your exit!
-我可以做個觀察嗎？ -你可以出去。
Mr. Acuna, your overwhelming graciousness bewilders me.
Mr.Acuna你壓倒一切的親切讓我不知所措。
However, l bear no grudges.
但是，我不能忍受嫉妒。
When you change your mind, call me.
等你改變主意的時候再給我打電話。
Out of my sight!
從我的視野里消失！
Thank you again for your welcome.
再一次感謝你的歡迎。
You let that jumping jack in my office.
是你讓他進來搗亂的。
You'll pay for this with every drop of your anemic blood.
你將要為此付出代價，用你僅有的血液。
You nincompoop! You worm!
你這個傻子！蠕虫！
You're fired! Now get out and never come back, you diddling dimwit.
你被解雇了！現在馬上給我滾出去 永遠都不要回來。你這招搖撞騙的笨蛋。
''Diddling dimwit''?
招搖撞騙的笨蛋？
Welcome home, Papa.
歡迎回來，爸爸。
l could have sworn l heard you swearing.
我發誓我聽到你在吼叫。
Why, l thought you were--
你怎么會在這兒？我以為你在
Aren't you looking extraordinarily happy about something?
你看起來格外開心
-l am happy. -Couldn't be orchids, could it?
-我很高興。 -為了那些蘭花，對吧？
And l'll let you in on a secret.
而且我也要跟你分享一個秘密。
l know who's been sending me the flowers.
我終于知道是誰這些天來一直送我花。
You do? Now, look, darling, everything can be explained.
你知道了？你看，親愛的！ 這些我都可以解釋的。
-What do you mean? -Tell me what you're talking about.
-你在說什么？ -你先說你要說什么吧。
The orchids, the notes.
那些蘭花，那些便條。
-l know who sent them. -You do?
-我知道是誰送的了。 -是么？
-Well, you don't seem brokenhearted. -Well, why should l be?
-你怎么看起來一點也不傷心。 -為什么我要傷心？
-l'm glad you're taking it this way-- -Tell me what you're talking about.
-我很高興你用這種態度來處理。。 -求你了，你到底在說什么？
-Tell me who you're talking about. -Oh, Mr. Acuna?
-也許你先告訴我你在說誰比較好。 -哦，Mr.Acuna?
When you change your mind, l'll be up in Room 920.
你改變主意的話，來樓上920房間找我。
Oh, Papa, that's who l'm talking about. He's the one.
哦 ，爸爸，就是這個人。我說的就是他。
-He's what? -The one who's in love with me.
-他怎么了？ -他就是那個愛著我的人。
-He is not! -Oh, yes, yes.
-不是他！ -哦，是的，是的。
l saw him bring the orchids this afternoon.
我看到他今天下午來送花。
Oh, l remember. He sang at the wedding.
哦，我想起來了。他是在婚宴上唱歌的那個人。
l tell you, he's not the one who's been sending you the flowers!
我告訴你，他不是那個一直送你花的人！
lf he is, he's a pest! He's not only a pest, he's a dancer!
就算他是，他也是個害虫 不僅是害虫，一個舞者！
-How wonderful. l love-- -He's not for you! He's out of work!
-太棒了，我喜歡-- -他不是你要的，他正在失業！
Then you give him work, for me.
那么你就給我一份工作，為了我。
Don't tell me you could do anything so ghastly as to get mixed up with him.
別告訴我你會為了跟他攪在一起做任何事情。
And to think l was cool to him at the wedding.
想一想，婚宴那天我對他很冷酷。
l forbid you to fall in love with this man!
我禁止你愛上那樣一個人。
And besides, it's too late. He's going somewhere.
除此之外，已經太遲了 他要動身去別的地方了。
New York, l hope.
去紐約，我希望是。
Well, maybe l can change his mind.
是么？或許我可以令他改變主意。
You should read what he wrote to me.
你該看看他給我寫的那些卡片。
No. No, on second thought, l don't think your heart could stand it.
哦，不。仔細想想 我不認為你的心臟可以受得了。
-Anybody can write a love letter. -l'd like to see you try it.
-每個人都會寫情書。 -我倒愿意看你寫一封。
Anyway, he's not leaving South America...
不管怎樣，他不會從南美離開的。
...if l can help it. And l think l can.
...如果我可以改變的話。而且我認為我可以。
-What was his room number? -My mind's a blank. l've forgotten.
-他的房間號是多少？ -我的大腦一片空白。什么東西都忘了。
l haven't.
我可沒有。
920, please.
請接920房間。
You ask him to the house tonight.
你今晚請他到家里來。
What's gotten into you, Maria? Nice girls don't act this way.
你怎么了，Maria？ 有教養的女兒不會這么像你這樣。
-Nice girls don't feel the way l do. -Why, you're brazen.
-那是因為她們沒有我現在的感覺。 -天哪，你真臉皮厚。
How could l be...
怎么會呢？
-...with a heart like an ice cube? -l didn't say that.
-...特別是帶著一顆冰冷的心？ -我從來沒有那么說過。
That gleam in your eye has nothing to do with ice cubes. lt's predatory.
你眼里掠過的閃光一點兒也不像有一顆冰冷的心。
Maybe you're right.
也許你是對的。
-920, please. -All right.
-請接920房間。 -好了。
When l've signed those papers, l'll ask him.
我簽完那些文件就會叫他。
You're a very sweet papa.
你真是一個體貼的爸爸。
Oh, and l'll have to hurry. l've only got three hours to dress.
哦，那我就得快點了。我只有三小時換衣服。
Bye, sweets.
再見了，親愛的。
-Why did you have to tell him off? -Don't worry, he'll come around.
-你為什么要告訴他我們住在哪里？ -別擔心，他會來的。
Oh, you don't know him.
哦，你不知道他。
You know, Acuna is the most opinionated man in South America.
你知道，Acuna是整個南美最固執的人。
l'll show you.
你跟我過來。
See that nose?
你看到他的鼻子了么？
That nose shows opinionation.
那種鼻子就說明他固執。
His ears indicate mulishness.
他的耳朵就顯示了他的執拗。
His forehead slopes like a tin roof.
他的前額傾斜的像房檐。
-No intellect whatsoever. -What about his chin?
-不管怎么看都不聰明。 -他的下巴怎樣？
Oh, his chin clearly indicates weakness of character.
哦他的下巴明顯象征了他性格上的缺陷。
Handlebar mustache, no sense of humor.
八字胡，一點兒也不幽默。
His droopy eyelids indicate he's a dope.
他下垂的說明他是一個笨蛋
Very flattering, Cugat.
非常逼真，Cugat。
-Oh, Mr. Acuna. -The Sky Room is going to miss you.
-哦，Mr.Acuna。 -這間天空房間會想念你的。
ln the meanwhile, l will speak to Mr. Davis alone.
同時，我想要單獨跟Mr. Davis談談。
Sure, sure. Will you excuse me, please?
沒問題。 我先離開了。
Mr. Davis, l find myself in an embarrassing position.
Mr.Davis，我現在正處在一個尷尬的境地。
Think nothing of it, sir. We all make mistakes.
放輕松。人都會犯錯的。
-When do l start dancing? -You do not start dancing.
-什么時候要我跳舞？ -你不用跳舞。
-Didn't you come to see about--? -One of my daughters.
-你來不是為了-？ -我的一個女兒。
The one you so gallantly referred to as the ''inside of a refrigerator.''
就是那個“從冰箱里面拿出來”的 你熱烈追求的那一個。
But l'm afraid l don't follow you.
我不明白你在說什么。
She thinks you're in love with her.
她以為你正瘋狂的愛著她。
Would it be rude of me to inquire if there's any insanity in your family?
恕我無禮的問一句 難道你們家人都錯亂么？
And what's worse, she has the illusion that she's in love with you.
更糟糕的是 她自己幻想她愛上了你。
-Oh, my. Poor child. -lt's not her fault. lt's yours.
-哦天哪，多可憐的孩子。 -這不是她的錯，是你的。
-l still don't follow you. -You took her the orchids, didn't you?
-我還是不明白你在說什么。 -你給她送去的蘭花，不是么？
Why, l left some orchids at your door, yes.
我是送去了一些蘭花。
But what's that got to do with the idea l'm in love with your daughter?
但是那跟我愛上你女兒有什么關系。
She's been receiving orchids and love notes from an unknown admirer.
一直有一個無名的仰慕者 給她送花和情書。
-Then she thinks l'm the fellow? -So you've stirred her imagination.
-然后她就認為我是那個家伙么？ -正是你激起了她的幻想。
l don't want to stir her imagination. l didn't write any notes.
我不想激起她的幻想。 我也沒有寫任何的便條。
Don't you think l know that? l wrote those notes myself.
你以為我不知道么？ 那些便條正是我寫的。
-You? Then there is insanity. -No, there isn't.
-你？這真瘋狂。 -不是你想的那樣。
All you've got to do is to let her think you wrote those notes.
你所要做的是就是 讓她相信是你寫的那些便條。
-l see. Then what? -Then disillusion her.
-我明白了。然后呢？ -然后敲醒她。
-Tell her l didn't send the flowers? -Of course not.
-告訴她花并不是我送的？ -當然不是。
Her pride would be crushed. She's got to believe that you admire her...
她的自尊心會被摧毀的 她已經相信你仰慕她。
...and yet for her own happiness, she's got to lose her infatuation for you.
...而且為了她的幸福，你也不能 她必須自己對你失望。
That's easy. Just tell her l'm a heel.
那很容易，直接告訴她我是跳舞的。
l want her to discover that for herself.
我想要她自己發現這一點。
Yeah? How?
但是怎么發現？
By being your own obnoxious self when you come to my house tonight.
今晚你帶著你那令人討厭的 個性到我家來。
Oh, l'm coming to your house tonight?
哦，我今晚要去你家？
To complete the disillusionment...
為了讓她徹底的醒悟
...you'll tell her you're sailing for North America tomorrow.
你必須跟她說你明天就要去北美了。
But l'm not. l like it here.
但是我并不會。我喜歡呆在這兒。
l'll pay your transportation and a bonus as well.
我會付你的旅費另外再給你一筆錢的。
Thanks just the same, Mr. Acuna.
Mr. Acuna.你的好意我心領了，Mr.Acuna。
My only interest at the moment is in your Sky Room.
我現在唯一感興趣的就是在你的天空房間里。
lf you do this for me, l'll give you a contract to dance, at some future date.
如果你為我這樣做了 將來我會跟你簽一個請你跳舞的合同。
Will you put that in writing and leave the date open?
你會寫下這些，而且日子隨我挑？
-Yes. -Okay.
-當然。 -好的。
-What time shall l show up? -At 9:00.
-我什么時候去你家？ -9點的時候。
And don't stay too late.
而且別待太久。
-Something in my eye. -A keyhole, no doubt.
-我眼睛里進了東西。 -不用想了，就是鑰匙孔。
-Until tonight at 9. -And l won't stay too late.
-記得今晚9點。 -而且我也不會待太晚。
Look what we found.
快看我們找到了什么。
ls this your Robert Davis?
這就是你的Robet Davis？
That's the one. He brought the orchids.
就是他。 他帶來的蘭花。
He's ''The ldol of New York.''
他是“紐約的偶像”。
l like his smile...
我喜歡他的微笑。
-...and the twinkle in his eye. -Remember Mama's advice:
-...還有他眼里的光芒。 -記得媽媽的忠告。
Don't frighten him with your intelligence.
別讓你的聰明嚇到了他
-Just act simple and mysterious. -l know, make an entrance.
-就裝作你很單純和神秘。 -我知道，給他一個機會
Be casual, as though l didn't know he was coming.
裝作一次偶遇，就像我不知道他會來。
That's right. Come on, Cecy.
正是那樣。過來，Cecy。
Eduardo.
Eduardo.
-Do l look all right? -You're as beautiful as ever, my dear.
-我看起來還還好吧。 -你永遠都是那么美麗，親愛的。
lt just takes longer now.
只是現在要花更長的時間了。
Ouch!
阿！
Oh, l forgot. l had a pin in my mouth. Did it go in very deep?
哦，我忘記嘴里還有大頭針。 刺得深么？
l'll probably look like a Ubangi by midnight.
到半夜的時候我大概就像 一個烏班吉（非洲某部落）了。
Hurry, it's 9:00.
快一點，已經9點了。
lf you giggle again, l'm going to throw cold water in your face.
如果你再傻笑 我就會往你臉上潑冰水了。
You think Mr. Davis wants to marry into a family of gigglers?
你認為Mr.Davis愿意娶一個 有愛傻笑的家人的女人么？
Maria won't marry this young man. She's not going to like him.
不會跟這個年輕人結婚的。她不會喜歡他的。
He has absolutely no good qualities.
他十分明顯沒有什么好。
That's not for you to decide.
那可不是你來決定的。
l read in a book that a salmon swims miles and miles to find a mate...
我從書上讀到三文魚會 游很遠很遠去尋找伴侶。
...and Maria has swum long enough.
...Maria已經游得很遠了。
Maria is going to wait until the right man comes along.
Maria會一直等下去 直到那一個專屬她的男人出現。
Why should she? l didn't.
她為什么要等，我可沒有。
Oh, it's Mr. Davis. He can't meet us scattered around the hall.
哦，Mr.Davis來了 可不能讓他看到我們在大廳里游蕩。
-Hurry, Mama. -Come on.
-快一點，媽媽。 -過來。
-Good evening, Mr. Acuna. -Mr. Davis.
-晚上好，Mr.Acuna。 -Mr. Davis.
-Did you receive the contract? -Yes, sir.
-你收到合同了么？ -收到了，先生。
Then l can depend on you?
我可以放心依靠你了？
Don't worry, she'll be disillusioned.
別擔心，我會讓她醒悟的。
Maria, may l present Mr. Robert Davis.
Maria,我來跟你介紹 Mr. Robert Davis.
-We've met before, haven't we? -Yes. No.
-我們已經見過了，不是么？ -是的，哦沒有。
That is-- ln a way, but--
那是--某種形式上，但是--
We will translate that remarkable statement...
我們先見見其他人
...after you've met the rest of the family.
...再來繼續
This is Mrs. Acuna. My daughters Cecy and Lita.
這是Mr. Acuna，我的女兒Cecy 和Lita
Mr. Robert Davis. He can't stay long.
Mr. Robert Davis. 他不能待很長的時間
Sit down, Mr. Davis.
請坐，Mr. Davis
l accidentally read one of your beautiful notes to Maria.
我很偶然的讀到了你寫給Maria的華麗的便條。
lt's a shame that such a talented young man is unemployed, Eduardo.
這么有才華的年輕人居然沒有被雇佣 真是可惜，Eduardo
Oh, but didn't Mr. Acuna tell you?
哦，Mr. Acuna 沒有告訴你們么？
l'm to dance in his Sky Room starting tomorrow night.
我從明天晚上開始將在他的天空房間跳舞。
-lsn't that so, Mr. Acuna? -The date was left open.
-是么？Mr. Acuna？ -日子還沒有定好。
-But you meant tomorrow, didn't you? -Oh, of course he did.
-你是指明天，不是么？ -哦，當然，他會的。
And you're going to love working for Papa. lsn't he?
你會覺得跟爸爸一起工作很愉快的。是吧，爸爸？
Oh, l'm sure l will. Oh, l almost forgot.
哦，這是肯定的。 哦，我差一點兒忘了。
These are for you. There's no note this time, because--
這是給你的。 這一次沒有寫便條，因為--
l'd rather you'd say what you might have written anyway.
我情愿你親口說出來。
-Do you mind if l smoke? -Oh, of course not.
-你們介意我抽煙么？ -當然不會。
No, thank you.
不用了，謝謝。
Have l said something wrong?
我說錯了什么么？
He thinks it's real.
他以為這是真槍。
l had it made into a cigarette lighter, Mr. Davis.
我叫人把它做成打火機，Mr. Davis.
Oh, l see. For a moment, it looked real.
原來是這樣。 乍看之下就像真的一樣。
Oh, l guess it's killed many a man in its day...
我猜它曾經殺了很多男人。
...but it's only an antique now.
...現在卻只不過是一個古董。
But you wouldn't mind pointing it that way a little bit?
你不會介意朝另一個方向指著吧？
-Of course not, but it's harmless. -Oh, l'm sure it is.
-當然不會，但是這把槍不會傷人的。 -當然它不會。
Do you mind? l could stand a little air.
如果你不介意的話 我可以有一些空間。
There's lots of it in the garden.
花園里還有很多的。
Remember?
記得么？
-What if l'd killed him? -Never mind him.
-我剛剛差點殺了他 -別管他了。
What about the vase?
倒是那個花瓶怎么辦？
Oh, now he'll never get back into a romantic mood.
哦，這下他不會有浪漫的心情了。
Maybe some music would quiet his nerves. Come on.
音樂可以平扶他的的神經，快走。
After my notes, l must be an awful disappointment to you.
跟我的便條相比，我一定讓你失望了。
Oh, on the contrary.
恰恰相反。
l like modest men.
我喜歡謙虛的男人。
Well, l don't know exactly how to tell you, but--
我不知道怎么跟你開口，但是--
l like bashfulness too.
我也喜歡容易害羞的男人。
Your city is so cosmopolitan, and this shack of yours is so magnificent...
你們的城市里有來自各地的人 你們家也是這么堂皇。
...frankly, l feel like a duck out of water.
...老實說，我覺得自己有些格格不入。
l think you'd fit in anyplace.
我覺得你能適合任何地方。
But l mean, l wouldn't fit into this kind of life, your kind of life.
但是我覺得，我不能適應 這種生活,你的生活。
l don't like it much either.
我也不怎么喜歡。
But you don't know my kind of life.
但是你不知道我的生活是怎樣的。
-lt's music and dancing, isn't it? -Yes.
-全是音樂和舞蹈，不是么？ -沒錯。
Well, we love your North American music and dances down here.
我們喜歡你們北美的音樂和舞蹈。
Oh, but imagine a man like me having to dance for a living.
但是你想想我是一個靠跳舞維生的男人。
l can't imagine a happier way to earn one.
我想象不出另一種更快樂的活法。
There's a great weakness in my character.
我的性格也有缺陷。
-l'm a sucker for a horserace. -They thrill me too.
-我沉迷于賽馬 -那也讓我激動得發抖。
l'd probably bet my last cent on a horse. As a matter of fact, l did.
我可能會把口袋里的最后一分錢 都賭在馬上事實上，我也是這么做的。
l have a gambler's heart myself.
我打心眼里也是個賭徒。
You know...
你知道
...l think that's why your notes intrigued me so.
...我想那就是為什么你的便條可以這么吸引我。
Look, little lady, as they'd say in Brooklyn:
你看，就像他們在布魯克林說的一樣：
''l can't bat in your league.'' l'm a plain, ordinary guy from Omaha, Nebraska.
我不能適應你們的生活,我只是內部 拉斯加州一個平凡的朴素的奧馬哈人。
Just an old-fashioned, everyday Middle Westerner.
全都是老式的，每天都是在美國中西部。
Why, my grandfather was a cattle raiser.
我的爺爺是養牛的。
So was mine!
我的也是！
But you're streamlined. You're today.
但是你的生活改進了，你活在今天。
Sister, l was raised amongst the grasshoppers. l am strictly from corn.
我是在田間長大的，吃的都是玉米。
I am not such a clever one
我對于最新的時尚
About the latest fads
可沒有那么敏感
I admit, I was never one
我必須承認，我也從來沒有
Adored by local lads
被某個本地年輕人吸引過。
Not that I ever try to be a saint
并不是我嘗試作一個聖徒。
I'm the type
我就是這一型的。
-That they classify as quaint -Quaint
-被他們當成奇怪的一類。 -奇怪的。
Must be another you
一定是另一個你。
I like the other you
我喜歡那另一個你。
I'm old-fashioned
我是守舊的。
I love the moonlight
我愛這月光。
I love
我愛
The old-fashioned things
那些老式的東西。
The sound of rain
下雨的聲音
Upon a window pane
在窗棱上
The starry song
星星般閃光的歌曲
That April sings
四月在歌唱
This year's fancies
這是一個奇異的年
Are passing fancies
那些短暫的美好
These my heart understands
這是我的心聽到的
I'm old-fashioned
我是守舊的人。
But I don't mind it
但是我不在乎
That's how I want to be
這就是我想要的
As long as you agree
只要你也愿意
To stay old-fashioned
一起守舊。
With me
與我一起。
lt's getting late, Mr. Davis.
已經很晚了，Mr.Davis。
-lt's your play, Eduardo. -Well, l don't want that card.
-到你了，Eduardo。 -我不要那張卡片。
Rummy.
拉米。
Am l the first girl you never kissed?
我是你第一個不愿意吻的女人么？
l knew a fellow once who came to a lull like this with a girl and--
我知道有一個家伙遇到像這樣 安靜的場合，跟一個姑娘在一起。。
Yes?
然后呢？
He didn't know what to say.
他不知道要說什么。
l heard of a man once who was in love with a girl...
我聽說過有一個男人愛上一個女人。。
...and afraid to say so.
...但是卻不敢說出來。
Cugat. l promised to meet him.
Cugat,我答應去見他。
l almost forgot. You'll forgive me if l go, won't you?
我差一點忘記了，你會原諒我現在離去吧？
-Of course. -l'm awfully sorry. l promised to see--
-當然。 -真的十分抱歉，但是我答應去見。
Good night.
晚安。
-Why, he's leaving. -Good.
-怎么了,他怎么走了？ -太好了。
Mr. Davis.
Mr. Davis.
-Doesn't Maria dance beautifully? -Yes.
-難道Maria跳得不美么？ -沒錯。
You should've seen her dressing for you.
你應該也看到她特意為你換的衣服吧？
No dress was good enough, even though she has dozens.
她從几十件里面挑選，哪一件都難滿她的意。
-Not that she's extravagant, Mr. Davis. -l'm sure she's not. Good night, girls.
-并不是她很奢侈，Mr. Davis。 -我肯定她不是，晚安了，姑娘么。
When Mama was away once, Maria ran the house herself.
有一次媽媽生氣出走，Maria一個跑出去找她。
-Papa said the bills were cut in half. -And what meals we had!
-爸爸說賬單可以少付一半了。 -我們吃的那是什么食物阿！
-Maria majored in domestic science. -She did?
-Maria是學家政學的。 -是么？
Everyone remarks on what a perfect wife she'll make.
每個人都說她會是一個完美的太太。
l agree. Absolute-- lf l could just have my hat.
肯定是- 可以把我的帽子遞給我么？
-Oh, of course. -You must forgive the girls...
-當然。 -你得原諒那些姑娘們。
...they're just anxious for Maria to get married so they can be married.
...她們實在是太想Maria嫁 出去了好讓她們可以結婚。。
-Well, thank you very much-- -They don't need to worry any longer.
-非常感謝。 -從今晚看來她們不用等太久了。
-l'd say Maria's falling in love. -We'd miss her if she left.
-我敢說Maria已經愛上了你。 -她跟你去紐約之后我們會想她的。
We'd be willing to make the sacrifice for her happiness.
但是我們愿意為了她的幸福做出犧牲。
Thanks. lt's been so nice.
謝謝，實在是太好了。
-Leaving so soon, Mr. Davis? -Yes.
-這么快就要走了，Mr. Davis? -是的。
But l hate to.
雖然我十分不愿意。
-Good night.
-晚安。
-Thanks a lot. -Oh, you're very welcome.
-謝謝你們的招待。 -不用客氣。
Will you three stop interfering with Maria's life?
你們三個不能停止干涉Maria的生活么？
Will you leave that to me?
讓我來處理好么？
-Oh, Maria!
-Oh, Maria!
-lsn't he just wonderful? -How'd you make out?
-他實在是太棒了。 -你覺得怎樣？
The first time in my life l ever really wanted a man to kiss me...
這是我這輩子第一次想讓一個男人吻我
...and he had something else to do.
...而他卻有其他的事情要做。
But the next time, it's going to be different.
但是下一次，就不會像這樣了。
Eduardo, did you hear that?
Edardo,你聽見了嗎？
-Hi, Fernie. -Oh, no. Over my dead body.
-你好，Fernie。 -哦，不，我死也不會讓你進去。
-l'm not going to get fired again today. -Must you clutter up the doorway?
-今天我可不想再被炒魷魚了。 -你可以不堵在門口嗎？
-You betrayed me last night. -Me? How?
-你昨晚違背了協議。 -我？哪里？
By deliberately concealing your true and obnoxious nature...
你故意隱瞞你那令人厭惡的個性
-...and making yourself be charming. -l did not.
-...而且還故作迷人的。 -我可沒有。
Maybe there is insanity in the female branch of the family.
可能是這個家庭的女人們都有些錯亂。
They've conceived a misguided affection for you.
她們似乎都對你有錯誤的評價。
-They think l'm in love with Maria. -The mention of love between you...
-她們都以為我愛上了Maria。 -在你和我女兒之間提到愛情這個字眼
...makes my flesh creep.
...讓我起疙瘩。
How you can be the father of such a lovely girl absolutely amazes me.
我很驚訝一個那么可愛的 姑娘竟有你這樣一個父親。
-l resent that remark. -l resent how you butt into her life.
-我不喜歡那個形容詞。 -我也看不慣你插手她的生活。
But you have absolutely no right to resent anything.
但是你并沒有任何權力抱怨。
Mr. Acuna, l've arranged to fly back to New York by the next plane.
Acuna先生我打算乘下一班飛機回紐約了。
-You've what? -You can tear up that contract.
-什么？ -你可以撕掉這份合約。
-l've decided to beat it. -Oh, you have? Just like that?
-我已經決定要走了。 -你已經決定了？僅此而已？
Yes, sir, l'm going to dump your entire asinine predicament...
是的先生，我要徹底的 離開這場愚蠢的鬧劇。
...right back into your lap.
...right back into your lap.
Oh, l see. You want them to think that l forced you to leave.
哦我懂了，你想讓她們認為是我逼你離開的。
lsn't that exactly what you're doing?
你不就是這個意思嗎？
You want Maria to think you're a martyr, sacrificed on the altar of love.
你想讓Maria認為你是這場愛情的受害者。
That idiotic statement didn't come from your wife's side of the family.
現在你要知道那種家庭性的錯亂 并不是從你的妻子那邊帶進來的。
Mr. Davis, you signed a binding contract with me.
先生，不要忘了我們是簽了合同的。
You'll stay here, or l'll file an injunction.
你必須待在這里，非則我會以次起訴你。
-Yesterday, you wanted-- -That was before...
-等等，你昨天還要我-- -那是之前
...your hideous display of charm last night. Now l have a new plan.
...由于你昨晚丑惡的展示你的魅力 現在我有一個新的計划。
You will live up to your contract in the Sky Room...
你必須完成我們在天空房間的合約
-...but you will keep away from Maria. -ls that supposed to be brilliant?
-...而且你要保証離Maria遠遠的。 -那會是明智之舉嗎？
That will let her know that you merely used her to get the contract.
那樣就會讓她知道你接近她 只是為了跟我簽這份合約。
Naturally, then, she will loathe you.
自然而然的她就會厭惡你。
That's just dandy. Then what?
那實在是太好了，然后呢？
Then, to show you how little you've meant to her...
然后再讓她知道你對她來說一點也不重要。
...she will immediately fall in love with a more acceptable young man.
她馬上就會其他的更好的年輕人吸引。
One of many whom l will invite to my home in the immediate future.
不久的將來我就會邀請 他們中的一個到家里來做客。
-You think she'll fall in love quickly? -Mr. Davis...
-你確定她會很快的愛上別人？ -Davis先生
...l have an instinct about emotional responses of the feminine heart.
...我對于女人感性心理的直覺很敏銳。.
Don't you think l ought to explain to Maria that--?
你不覺得我該跟Maria解釋--
No.
不用。
-Why, l thought perhaps-- -No.
-但是我覺得的如果-- -沒有如果。
Our mutual aim is that she loathe you, isn't it?
我們共同的目的就是讓她討厭你，不是么？
l guess so.
我想是的。
-l was just thinking-- -No.
-我只是在想-- -No.不用想。
You do the dancing, l'll do the thinking.
你跳你的舞，我來想。
Fernando, in making out the guest list for the wedding anniversary ball...
在寫我結婚周年紀念舞會的客人名單時，
...I wanna include the most outstanding and charming men...
我要加上那個去過我家的
...who have ever been guests in my home.
...迷人的年輕人。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Wait a minute! l thought l discharged you yesterday!
等等，我記得我昨天把你炒魷魚了。
Mrs. Acuna told me to forgive your display of temper, so l have.
太太讓我千萬要原諒 你的壞脾氣，我不能推辭。
l forgive you, Mr. Acuna.
所以我原諒你了，Acuna先生。
Oh, thank you very much.
哦，那可真謝謝你。
Not at all, sir. l'll prepare the list.
不用客氣先生。我會准備客人名單的。
''Mr. and Mrs. Acuna request the pleasure of your company...
先生和太太要請你們出席
...at the 25th anniversary of their wedding.
...她們25周年紀念
Fancy dress.''
化妝舞會。
l can't believe it's been 25 years, Delfina.
我簡直不能相信已經25年了,Delfina。
That's because you aren't married to Eduardo.
那是因為不是你嫁給Eduaroda。
l might have been if you hadn't seen him first.
我可能會，如果不是你先遇見他的話。
-Where's Maria? -Tennis lesson.
- Maria在哪兒？ -她在上網球課。
But her mind isn't on the ball.
但是她的心可不在那兒。
She's still trying to figure out why Mr. Davis didn't kiss her, l guess.
我猜她還是在想為什么 那晚Davis先生沒有吻她。
-Oh, hello, Fernando. -Good afternoon, Lita...
-哦，你好Fernando。 -下午好，Lita。
...Mrs. Acuna, Castro, Cecy.
...Acuna夫人，Castro,Cecy你們好。
Mr. Acuna sent me with his approved list of young men he wishes invited.
先生要我送來他想邀請的年輕人的名單。
-Oh, swell! -Let me see.
-哦，真不少！ -讓我看看。
l don't see Mr. Davis' name here, Fernando. Mr. Robert Davis.
我沒有看見Davis先生的名字Fernando 是Robert Davis.
lt seems that Mr. Robert Davis is not on Mr. Acuna's approved list.
似乎Robert Davis先生沒有 受到Acuna先生的邀請。
He's the only one on my list.
他只在我的名單上。
-Hello, Aunt Maria. -Hello.
-你好，Maria阿姨。 -你好。
-Fernando.
-Fernanado你好。
Do you know why Papa left Mr. Davis off the list?
你知道為什么爸爸沒有 把Davis先生加在這個名單上么？
He said something about Mr. Davis devoting himself to the Sky Room...
他好像說了一些關于Davis 從現在開始要一心一意的
-...from now, henceforth. -Thank you, Fernando.
-...投入到天空房間的表演中去。 -謝謝你，Fernando。
You know, we're expecting you at the celebration.
你知道我們也希望你出現在舞會上。
Thank you, Mrs. Acuna. You honor me. Sweet.
謝謝你，Acuna太太，我很榮幸。
-Bye. -Goodbye, Fernando.
-再見 -再見，Fernando。
l'd be interested in meeting your Robert Davis, Maria.
我倒是很想見見你的Robert Davis，Maria。
Well, l haven't a thing to do right now.
我現在就有空啊。
How nice. Neither have l.
正好，我也有空。
A little faster, Cugie, please. Once more.
這一段請再快點。 再來一次。
One, two.
一，二。
Hold it.
暫停。
Well, hello.
你好。
-Does your father know you're here? -No, why should he?
-你爸爸知道你在這兒嗎？ -不，為什么一定要他知道？
-Mrs. Castro, may l present-- -Why, l remember you.
-Castro太太，讓我來介紹一下-- -我記得你。
-So you're Maria's Robert. -Yes-- Well, l don't know. Am l?
-你就是Maria的Robert。 -是-恩，我不知道，我是嗎？
Won't you come in and sit down?
快進來請座。
We are special emissaries from Mr. and Mrs. Acuna.
我是Acuna先生特別派來的使者。
We're asking the pleasure of your company on Wednesday evening.
我們來邀請你參加星期三晚上的晚會。
-Thank you. -At 9 p.m., but...
-謝謝你們。 -晚上9點開始，但是
...you can come earlier if you like.
...如果你愿意的話可以早點來。
Are you sure Mr. Acuna wants me to come?
你確定Acuna先生想讓我去嗎？
Oh, he'd be devastated if you didn't.
如果你不去他會很傷心的。
And so would l.
我也是。
You were coming back in half an hour, weren't you, Auntie?
你會在半個小時之后回來，不是嗎？阿姨？
Oh, yes, in a half an hour. Goodbye.
哦，是的是的，半個小時之后。再見了。
Won't you sit down?
請座。
Well, this is a pleasant surprise.
這可真是一個驚喜阿。
We were just running over a little thing from Harlem.
我們剛剛在排練一些黑人的音樂。
But l don't suppose you've heard of Harlem here.
但是我想你在這兒可能沒有聽過黑人的文化。
lsn't that where the zoot suit with the reet pleat comes from?
是不是那種帶褶皺的阻特妝的來源？
Yeah.
正是。
-l'd like to hear it. May l? -Certainly.
-我想聽聽看，可以嗎？ -當然。
Oh, Cugie, let's have it.
哦，Cugie咱們來一段。
Just heard of the Shorty George
剛剛聽說矮子喬治。
Got word of the Shorty George
聽到矮子喬治的消息。
Seems that it's a kind of jig
就像是一種玩笑一樣。
Named for someone about so big
因為只有這么大才得了個這種名字。
He rambles around the town
他在城中游蕩。
Preambles around the town
給陌生人導游。
Then steps on a crowded street
有一天走上了擁擠的街道。
And beats his feet till his feet is beat
腳不停的打著節奏。
Watch him go
仔細看
And he can
他可以
Like a real
像一個
Natural man
真正的正常人
High stepper is Shorty George
矮子喬治跳舞跳得好
Black pepper is Shorty George
矮子喬治是黑胡椒
He dances to pay the rent
他靠跳舞維生
And to see that you're solid sent
看你是否打賞
Say, mister, can you spare a penny?
像這樣，先生，能打賞一個便是嗎？
Lady, can you spare a dime?
小姐，可以打賞10便士嗎？
He makes I don't know how many
我不知道 他賺了多少錢
Because he's dancing all the time
但是他一直在跳舞
Papa's dressed up mighty sporty
爸爸穿得像運動員
Mama's snoozing in the shade
媽媽在樹蔭里打盹
But while Mama's catching 40
40當媽媽到40歲的時候
Shorty sees the rent is paid
矮子發現租金已經付完了
Get hip to the Shorty George
為矮子喬治喝彩
Hop, skip to the Shorty George
為矮子喬治跳躍
Directions are short and sweet
地址很短也很甜蜜
I know you'll beat your feet Until your feet is beat
我知道你會不停的這樣跳下去
Are you sure he's coming?
你確定他回來嗎？
Does Papa know?
爸爸知道嗎？
Do you think he'll propose tonight?
你想他今晚會不會像你求婚？
Well, if he doesn't, it won't be my fault.
如果他沒有的話，那可不是我的錯。
Maria!
Maria!
My, isn't Papa handsome?
哦，天哪，爸爸真帥！
Just think, Papa, you've been married longer than we've lived.
想想看，爸爸你結婚的 時間比我們的年齡都大，
Well, l consider that a very fortunate coincidence, my dear.
我認為那是一個非常幸福的巧合。
Maria.
Maria.
lt just occurred to me that l neglected to ask Mr. Davis...
不幸的是我忘記邀請Davis先生今晚到我們家來。
...to come to the house tonight. That doesn't bother you, does it?
...你不介意吧？
-Should it, Papa? -lt's just, l thought it unforgivable...
-他該不該被邀請呢，爸爸？ -我只是在想他沒有再找過你
...that he didn't call on you after starting his contract with me.
...自從我跟他簽了合約以后 這實在是不可原諒。
He hasn't sent any more orchids, has he?
他再也沒有送過什么花了，不是嗎？
-No more notes? -Nope.
-也沒有便條了？ -沒有
-You don't seem upset about it. -l'm not.
-你看起來一點也不沮喪。 -我沒有。
Well, that's fine.
那太好了。
There'll be some handsome young men tonight.
今晚會有一些英俊的年輕人
l want you to have a happy time.
我希望你有一個快樂的時光。
l expect this to be the happiest night of my life.
我覺得這會是我一生中最幸福的夜晚。
That's a good girl. l knew you'd let Mr. Davis know exactly where he stands.
那才是我的好女兒,我就知道你會 讓Davis先生知道他到底有多少斤兩。
Yes, Papa, that's just what l intend to do.
是的，爸爸。 那正是我打算要做的.
Papa, Grandma's here. Hurry!
爸爸，奶奶來了，快過來！
Thank you very much. Very kind of you.
謝謝你。 很高興見到你。
-Congratulations. -Oh, Maria.
-祝賀你。 -哦，Maria。
What's going on between your wife and my husband?
你的太太跟我的先生在干什么呢？
They're always whispering.
他們總是在說悄悄話。
This is a fine time to suspect your husband...
這可不是一個好機會去懷疑你丈夫的不忠
...on your wedding anniversary.
...在你們結婚周年紀念會上。
Well, l don't know.
誰知道呢？
You're such a fool, and you think you're so smart.
你只是一個小笨蛋，但你卻認為你很聰明。
Why, Maria actually seemed happy...
誰說的，Maria看起來挺高興的
...when l told her l hadn't invited Mr. Davis.
...當我告訴她我沒有邀請Davis先生時。
Robert.
Robert.
-Oh, Mr. Davis. -We're so glad to see you.
-哦，Davis先生。 -見到你實在是太高興了。
Thank you. Congratulations, Mrs. Acuna.
謝謝你們。 祝賀你，Acuna小姐。
-lt's so nice of you to ask me. -We're happy to have you, aren't we?
很高興你邀請我。 有你參加我們會很高興的，不是嗎？Maria？
-Delighted. Aren't we, Papa? -Yes, indeed.
-是很高興，不是嗎？爸爸？ -當然。
Congratulations, Mr. Acuna.
祝賀你，Acuna先生。
lt gives us all an opportunity to say goodbye to him.
這給了我們大家一個機會跟他道別。
-Goodbye?
-道別？
He received an offer from New York, didn't you, Robert?
他接到紐約的一份工作，不是嗎？Robert?
-Well, that is-- -lnsisted on taking tomorrow's plane.
-事實上是-- -而且他執意明天就乘飛機走。
Didn't you, Robert?
不是嗎？Robert?
Yes, l guess l did.
是的，我想我是的。
-Oh, Mr. Davis, you can't! -We won't let you!
-哦，Davis先生，你不能！ -我們不會讓你這么干的！
l'm sure Mr. Davis knows what's best.
我肯定Davis先生知道什么才是最好的選擇
-For him. -You must induce him to stay.
-對他自己來說。 -你必須勸他留下。
l have no alternative. He asked me to tear up the contract.
我沒有選擇的余地，他要求我撕毀合同。
-Didn't you, Robert? -Yes, sir.
-不是這樣嗎？Robert？ -是的。
Grandma wanted to meet you.
奶奶想要見你。
-lsn't she a lovely girl? -l've never met a lovelier one.
-她是一個可愛的姑娘，不是嗎？ -是我見過最可愛的。
Remember, l have my own chapel at home...
記住，我在家里有自己禮堂
...if you'd like to get married without the usual Acuna fuss.
...如果你們想清清靜靜的結婚的話 可以的用得著。
Granny, we....
奶奶，我們。。
You don't understand. We have no use for a chapel.
你弄錯了。 我們還用不上禮堂。
We've just heard that Mr. Davis is forced to leave us.
我們剛聽說Davis先生要被迫離開我們。
You chose exactly the right word, Maria.
你選擇的恰當的詞語，Maria。
Our dear friends, 52 years ago in a little village in Brittany...
親愛的朋友們，在52年前 在布列塔尼一個小村子里
...my beloved mother and father were married.
...我可愛的媽媽和爸爸結婚了。
When they came to South America they brought a song...
后他們來到南美并且帶來了一首歌
...and a happy tradition with them.
...以及保持快樂的傳統。
This music was played at their wedding...
這首歌曾經在他們的婚宴上彈奏過
...and 25 years ago, at Delfina's and mine.
...并且在25年前，在Delfina和 我的婚宴上也彈奏過。
And now, in honor of my beloved mother...
現在，作為對我可愛的母親的敬意...
...and in tribute to my charming wife...
...和對我迷人的太太的禮物...
...l have asked Mr. Cugat to play that music for us tonight.
...我托Cugat先生今晚為大家演奏這首曲子。
Listen to the birdies Letting those squeaks out
聽聽著鳥叫聲讓它們快樂的歌唱
Puffing their cheeks out All around the place
讓它們到處溜達
Little hurdy-gurdies Sounding so merry
小小手風琴 聲音多么愉快
Getting so very blue in the face
它的臉變得那么藍
Surely there's a reason Everybody's gay
大家這么快樂當然是有原因的
It must be the season For a wedding day
這一定是結婚的季節
Ding-dong dell The bells in the steeple go
塔尖的鐘叮當響
Around the countryside
叮當的響聲傳遍鄉野
Ding-dong dell And off all the people go
叮當的響，大家都聚在一起
Off to kiss the bride
親吻新娘
All the donkey carts are driving
所有的驢車都在飛奔
To the wedding in the spring
去趕春天的婚禮
All the neighborhood's arriving
鄰居們都來了
To see the wedding ring
為了瞧一眼結婚戒指
Now they're forming in a column
現在他們都站成几隊
For the service has begun
儀式就要開始了
Although the padre's solemn He's the only one
神父的表情嚴肅，他可是唯一的一個
Down the aisle The page and the flower girls
走過過道 侍童和撒花的姑娘們
In a while The happy bride and groom
緊接著就是幸福的新郎新娘
The ladies smile We'll give her a shower, girls
女人們都笑了 我們要給她潑潑水，姑娘們
Dishes and a broom
清洗和去除不快樂的東西
All the gentlemen are jolly For the wine is flowing free
先生們都愉快的喝著紅酒
All the ladies melancholy For the days that used to be
女人們都很憂郁，過去的日子不再復返
When the carriage That's been waiting
久等的車夫
Takes the newlyweds away
把這對新婚的人兒帶走
The crowd keeps celebrating Till the break of day
人們還在慶祝，直到晚上
Ding-dong dell The bells in the steeple go
塔尖的鐘叮當響
Around the countryside
叮當的響聲傳遍鄉野
Ding-dong dell Toast the bride
向這對新人們敬酒
Then farewell Off they ride
然后再跟他們永別
Oh, what fun
真好
Comes under the heading Of wedding in the spring
來到春天這個結婚的季節里
Hey, you've got to make Davis so jealous that he won't leave Maria.
對了，你們必須讓Davis嫉妒，讓他不會離開Maria
lf he takes a plane, it's gotta be on a honeymoon with her.
如果他上了那般飛機 那必須是他們在一起度蜜月。
Will you do it?
快去做。
Well, well, what are you waiting for?
你還在等什么？
Listen, old man, l started this dance with Maria, and l'm going to finish it.
聽著，你這老家伙 這場舞是我開始的，我要把它跳完。
Go out there and cut in on him.
快出去，把他們兩個分開。
Keep after him until he's so jealous he can't stand it.
一直跟著他，直到他嫉妒。 他不能忍受的。
Help!
救命啊。
Mr. Davis, how dare you attack a guest of mine!
先生，你怎么敢攻擊我的客人！
-The jester was getting out of hand. -And getting in my hair.
-這個小丑在這里搗亂。 -還弄亂了我的頭發。
-l will not tolerate this sort of thing. -lt was our fault, we egged him on.
-我不能容忍這種事情發生。 -這是我們的錯，爸爸，是我們煽動他的。
But falling in the pool was his own fault!
但是掉到水池中是他自己的錯。
Everything that happens in the Acuna family is my fault.
家庭里出的所有的問題都是我的錯。
l work long hours, l do as l'm told, and where does it get me?
我加班，我聽從吩咐，但是看看我得到了什么？
ln the end?
最后？
Oh, so it's you! You chose your costume well, fool!
哦，是你啊！ 笨蛋，你選的服裝剛剛合適。
Mr. Acuna, l have stood enough.
Acuna先生，我已經受夠了！
Fernando, l didn't know. l guess it was partly my fault.
我不知道是你。我想我也有責任。
lt's not your fault l'm distantly related to this fuddy-duddy by marriage.
這不是你的錯。是我因為結婚的原因 跟這個嘮嘮叨叨的家伙竟然成了遠親。
-What was that again? -You will bark at me no longer!
-你敢再說一遍？ -你再也不能炒我魷魚了！
l resign, and don't take advantage of our family connections...
我辭職，別想用裙帶關系把我再弄回來。
...to try to get me back again. Fuddy-duddy.
...你這嘮嘮叨叨的老家伙。
Oh, let's tell the truth. We were trying to help ourselves.
我們說實話吧。我們是為自己好。
We're sick and tired of being old maids.
我們實在是厭倦了等待。
We wanted to make Robert jealous...
我們想讓Robert嫉妒
...so that he'd propose to Maria before he left.
...然后他就會在他離開之前向Maria求婚。
-You're wasting your time. -Well, why?
-你們是在浪費時間。 -為什么？
Because l'm not in love with Robert and he's not in love with me.
因為我不愛Robert， Robert也不愛我。
l think we've embarrassed him enough.
我想我們已經麻煩Robert夠了。
Don't let it upset you, Robert.
Robert.別為此沮喪，Robert。
Maria was bound to come to her senses sooner or later.
她終于看清你的面目了。
Kind of settles your problems, doesn't it?
也算解決了你的問題，不是嗎？
Would you mind if l said goodbye to her?
你介意我跟她說再見嗎？
Not at all, not at all.
一點也不。
Thanks.
謝謝。
Maria.
Maria.
Why did you say that to Robert out there?
你為什么剛剛那樣對Robert說？
What else could l say?
還有什么別的我能說的嗎？
Everybody's trying go push him into marrying me. Even Granny tried it.
每個人都在逼他娶我，奶奶也是。
lf you ask me, l don't think he needs any pushing.
如果你問我，我不覺得他是被逼。
Maria.
Maria.
There's something l've got to say.
有些事情我必須跟你說清楚。
Take her in the garden. You can say it much better out there.
帶她去花園。你們可以暢所欲言。
The air's nice out there, remember?
那里的空氣很好，記得嗎？
l just wanted to say that--
我只是想說--
Gee, you're beautiful.
天哪，你真美。
lt's funny, l had so much to say.
這很好笑，其實我有很多話想說。
And now l can't think of a darned thing.
但是我現在卻無法思考。
Where was l?
我說到哪兒了？
You said l was beautiful.
你說我很美。
Oh, yes, l did.
Oh, yes, l did.哦是的。
Look, would you mind turning the other way, please?
你介意轉過身去嗎？
Why?
為什么？
l can't concentrate when you look at me like that.
你那樣看著我讓我無法思考。
l was only kidding.
我只是開玩笑。
Oh, you're terrific!
哦，你實在是太棒了！
What's the use?
多浪費阿。
I was never able to recite a fable That would make the party bright
我從來都不會張口編出 美麗的故事讓晚會更加閃亮。
Sitting at the table I was never able
坐在桌子上，我從來都
To become the host's delight
不能使主人高興。
But now you've given me My after-dinner story
但是現在你已經給我了一個 可以茶余飯后談論的故事
I'll just describe you as you are In all your glory
我會用最華麗的詞藻形容你
You were never lovelier
你是最可愛的
You were never so fair
你是最美麗的
Dreams were never lovelier
美夢也沒有你可愛
Pardon me if I stare
請原諒我的目光被你吸引
Down the sky The moonbeams fly
天空下月光飛舞
To light your face
是為了照亮你美麗的臉龐
I can only say
我只能說
They chose the proper place
它們選擇了合適的地方
You were never lovelier
你是最可愛的
And to coin a new phrase
可愛的無法形容
I was never luckier
我從來沒有這么幸運
In my palmiest days
即使在我最有名的時候
Make a note And you can quote me
記下來，以便日后引用
Honor bright
無上的榮欣
You were never lovelier
你是最可愛的
Than you are tonight
在今晚
ls that what you wanted to say, Robert?
這就是你想說的嗎？
Well, that's only the first part.
這只是第一部分。
l don't quite know how to tell you the rest.
我并不知道怎么告訴你下一部分。
Well, maybe l can make it easy for you.
也許我可以幫你說。
l love you too.
我也愛你。
Oh, doctor, you've struck a nerve!
哦，醫生，你已經麻痺了我的神經。
Well, Robert, did you say goodbye?
你說了再見嗎？
Not exactly. lt was more like hello.
確切地說并沒有。 這更像一個問好。
l can never say goodbye to her, sir.
先生，我不知道怎么跟她說再見。
-l love Maria. -You don't say.
-我愛Maria。 -別這么說。
Well, that's just too bad.
那對你來說不是很糟嗎？
lt would be if she didn't love me too.
如果她不愛我的話確實是。
That's poppycock. You heard what she said.
胡說，你聽到她說過什么了。
Yep, l was there. You weren't.
是的，我聽到了，但是你不知道 你不在的時候她對我說什么。
-You're leaving on tomorrow's plane. -Yeah, but with Maria.
-但是你明天就要上飛機離開這里了。 -是的，和Maria一起。
You'll do nothing of the kind!
你不能怎么做！
Sit down, Robert, sit down.
先坐下來,Robert。
This is going to hurt you, and l admit, l'm sorry for you.
這可能會傷害你，我也很同情你。
Maria isn't in love with you. She merely thinks she is.
Maria愛上的并不是你，可能她以為她是的。
That's good enough for me.
這對我來說已經足夠了。
-How will she feel when she finds out? -Finds out what?
-等她知道真相的時候，你覺得她會怎么想？ -知道什么？
That you weren't her unknown admirer?
就是你并不是那一個無名的仰慕者
That you agreed to deceive her in exchange for a contract?
真相就是，你答應欺騙她是為了交換一份合同
Well, that's not a very pretty way to put it.
那可不是一個好的形容方式。
A woman doesn't mind you lying when you compliment her...
一個女人不會介意你稱贊她的時候撒謊...
...but she'd never forgive a lie that made her a moonstruck ninny.
...但是她永遠不能原諒別人把她當傻子。
She's not. And l haven't been exactly lying to her.
她不是傻子，而且我并沒有真正的欺騙她。
Besides, you got me into this.
而且，是你把我卷進來的。
Did you know that Maria found a romantic ideal at 1 5?
你知道Maria在15歲的時候就 開始幻想浪漫的事情嗎？
-No. -She did.
-不知道。 -她這樣做了。
His name was Lochinvar.
他的名字叫Lochinvar。
You don't mean that fellow on a white horse?
你不是說那騎白馬的家伙吧？
A sort of knight?
一個爵士？
She cherished a dream that she'd meet a man...
她一直希望有個男人
-...that measured up to that ideal. -l don't believe that.
-...能像Lochinvar一樣。 -我不相信。
She's a big girl now.
她現在已經長大了。
Have you taken a good look at her lately?
你最近有沒有仔細的看過她？
At heart, she's still the same romantic girl.
打心底講，她還是愛浪漫的小女孩兒。
You were just an accident, my boy. lt might have been anybody.
你只是一次偶然，我的孩子 換作任何人都可以。
Any man who arrived when she was ready and waiting...
在她准備好和等待的時候，來的不管是誰...
...for the lover who intrigued her, who brought her orchids.
...都可以僥幸得到她的愛 不管誰給她帶去蘭花。
There'd come a day when the illusion l created would vanish.
總有一天我親手創造的幻想會破滅。
Suddenly, she'd see you as you really are.
總有一天，她會突然發現那個真實的你。
And that's...? That's bad, huh?
那真糟糕，是吧？
For Maria, yes.
對Maria來說，是的。
Yeah.
對。
l'm sorry.
我很遺憾。
l try to appear hard, but l'm a fake, Robert.
我試著使自己看起來堅硬，但事實上我并不是。
At heart, l'm a sentimentalist.
其實，我是一個多愁善感的人。
l pity you, but l love my daughter.
我很同情你，但是我也愛我的女兒。
l want to see her happy. Don't you?
我想讓她開心，你也是，對嗎？
Of course l do.
那當然。
lf l go north, will you promise that she'll never know...
如果我去了北方，你可以保証她永遠不會知道
-...that l didn't send the notes? -l give you my word.
-...我并沒有給她送便條？ -我向你保証。
lt's just that l want her to remember me...
我只是想讓她記住
...as she thinks l am.
...在她記憶中的我。
l'll let her keep her memories.
我會讓她記住這美好的回憶的。
As a matter of fact, l'll compose a farewell note...
事實上，我會為你寫一份永別的便條
...that she'll treasure as long as she lives.
讓她一生珍藏。
lt's best that l don't see her again.
我不要再見她是最明智的選擇。
l wouldn't know what to say.
我一定說不出再見的。
l'll say it. l'll break it gently.
我會幫你說的。 我會幫你很委婉的結束。
Thank you, sir.
謝謝你，先生。
We're awfully sorry, Fernando.
我們十分抱歉， Fernando.
We didn't mean to get you in trouble.
我們并不想給你帶來麻煩。
l'm going to insist that Eduardo ignore his resignation.
我會讓Eduardo不管你的辭職信的。
Oh, Mama.
Oh, 媽媽。
While you're there, will you put in a good word for Robert?
你進去的時候能給Robert說些好話嗎？
Of course, dear.
當然，親愛的。
''Dearly beloved...
“我深愛的
...as long as my heart beats, l'll never forget the softness of your lips...
只要我的心臟還在跳動 我永遠也不能忘記你柔軟的雙唇
...the pounding of your heart against mine.
...我們重疊的心跳
Yes, my dearest, darling Maria...
是的，我最愛的人，我的Maria
...l will always cherish the exquisite torture of our stolen kisses...
我會永遠珍藏我們偷吻的甜蜜的折磨
...our sweet stolen moments together.
我們一起偷偷的幸福時光。
-Maria, my secret love.'' -Maria?
-Maria我秘密的愛人” -Maria?
You and Maria Castro!
你和Maria Castro!
Now l know what all that whispering's been about.
現在我知道你們那些悄悄話是在干什么了。
-You bluebeard! -Delfina, give me that note.
-你這沒良心的！ -Delfina, 把那個便條還給我。
The ''softness'' of her.... The ''pounding'' of her....
她“溫柔的” 她心跳的“撞擊聲”
To think that you, lovemaking with Maria.
你居然跟你孩子的教母
The godmother of your own child.
睡在了一起！
The wife of your best friend.
你最好朋友的妻子。
Writing a love note to her on our own wedding anniversary.
在我們的結婚紀念日上給她寫情書。
-You wretch! -Delfina, l can ex--
-你這不幸的人！ -Delfina, 我可以解-
Don't try to change the subject. Say something!
別想扯別的東西，你說啊！
Delfina, give me that note!
Delfina, 把那個便條還給我！
l regret having to say goodbye, Mrs. Castro. You've been most kind.
我很抱歉要說再見了，Castro太太，你是最和善的。
You'd better go into the library, Mrs. Castro.
你最好去一趟書房，Castro太太。
-Your name is being bandied about. -What's that?
-他們正在談論你呢。 -關于什么？
The pistols are on the table.
手槍在桌子上。
Retribution day is here. Acuna's going to get what's coming to him.
今天得到報應了，Acuna要為他做的付出代價。
-How? Why? -He was caught red-handed...
-怎樣？為什么？ -他被抓當場捉住
...writing a love note to Maria Castro.
寫情書給Maria Cstro。
Maria Castro?
Maria Castro?
-l'm innocent, l tell you. -Don't touch me, you scorpion.
-跟我無關，我告訴你。 -別碰我，你這毒蠍子。
Oh, Juan, we'll have to bear this disgrace together.
哦，Juan我們必須共同面對著恥辱。
And we have grown children.
我們都有已經長大成人的孩子。
This letter was written to your wife by my husband.
這封信是我的丈夫寫給你的妻子的。
Let the reptile's own words convict him.
讓這卑鄙的人自己寫的話告訴你他的罪狀。
We caught him writing it. He jumped like he was shot.
他在寫的時候剛好被我們碰到了 他給嚇了一跳。
-Did he admit it? -l admit nothing.
-他承認了嗎？ -我沒有什么好承認的。
You keep out of this! l'm talking to your wife.
你滾開！ 我在跟你的太太說話。
l gave him the best 25 years of my life.
我把我一生中最好的25年獻給了他。
Do you deny you wrote this note?
你否認你寫了這個便條嗎？
l ask that my daughters leave this ridiculous scene.
我要求我的女兒們離開這荒謬的場面。
And l demand that they stay.
但是我要他們都留下。
They'll learn a lesson in matrimony they'll never forget.
她們會學到一個結婚的教訓而且永遠不會忘記。
Eduardo, l am a jealous man.
Eduardo, 我是容易吃醋的男人。
Will you please take that injured look from your fat face?
你就不能不讓你肥胖的臉上 挂著一副受傷的表情？
-Did you write this note? -Yes, l wrote the note--
-這是你寫的嗎？ -是的，這是我寫得--
l'm sure that Papa can explain everything if you'll just give him time.
我肯定如果你們給他時間 他可以對這一切都做出解釋。
-Yes, if you'll just give me time. -Well, we're listening.
-沒錯，如果你們給我時間的話。 -好啊，我們在聽著呢。
Well, this isn't the time.
但是現在不是時候。
And what have you to say, you brazen thing?
你這厚顏無恥的家伙，你還要說什么？
My dear, sweet, darling wife, will you please shut up?
我親愛的可愛的妻子，你就不能閉嘴嗎？
l'm not speaking to her again anyway.
無論怎樣我也不會再跟她說話了。
lf you wanted my husband, why didn't you come to me and ask for him?
如果你想要我的丈夫 為什么你不直接跟我跟我要他呢？
l don't want your husband.
我并不想要你的丈夫。
There she goes, laughing at me behind my back.
是啊，她就是這樣，在我的背后偷笑。
Beg pardon, Delfina, right in your face.
糾正一下，親愛的Delfina，是當著你的面。
Oh, whispering women!
你這個愛撥弄是非的女人！
Going to his office every day, and him, writing letters!
你每天都去他的辦公室，而他呢，就給你寫信！
-He's a fiend. -You don't know...
-他就是一個魔王。 -你們不知道
-...what you're talking about. -Don't argue!
-...你們在說的是怎么一回事. -別狡辯了。
lf Delfina says he's a fiend, he's a fiend.
如果Delfina說他是魔王，他就是。
-They're insane, Maria, both of them. -l am insane, Eduardo.
-他們都在發神經，Maria，他們都是。 -我是發神經。
lt's an insane world when my best friend and my own wife--
這真是一個瘋狂的世界 當我的妻子和我最好的朋友--
Eduardo, we must confess.
Eduardo, 我們必須把真相說出來了。
Did you hear her? She wants to confess.
你聽到她說什么了嗎？她要坦白。
We'll confess nothing. Not here and not now.
我們沒有什么好坦白的 不是在這兒，也不是現在。
-You'll have to be patient. -l'll have to be patient?!
-你們兩個必須耐心一點。 -要我耐心一點？
Hold that gun. lt might go off, you know.
那好這把槍。 你知道，這可能會走火。
Now, look, l can explain everything.
現在，你們瞧，我可以解釋所有的事情。
Mr. Acuna was not writing that letter to Maria Castro.
Acuna先生的那封信不是給Maria Castro的.
He was writing it to Maria, his own daughter...
他是要寫給 Maria,他的女兒
-...as a farewell note from me. -From you?
-...作為我一個永別的留言 -你的？
He wrote all the notes you received, and he sent all the orchids.
你收到的便條都是他寫的 那些蘭花也是他送的。
l don't understand.
我不明白。
He just decided that Maria should have an unknown suitor, so--
他只是覺得Maria需要一個無名的仰慕者 所以--
ls that true, Eduardo?
這是真的嗎？ Eduardo?
You were very considerate, Papa.
你總是這么體貼周到，爸爸。
But how did you come into all this?
但是你是怎么卷進來的呢？
When l delivered the orchids, Maria, you jumped at conclusions.
我送那些蘭花的時候，Maria你誤會了。
So your father had to ask me to act as your admirer.
因此你的父親只有請我來扮演你的仰慕者。
Well, how did you bring yourself to make such a sacrifice?
你為什么要做這種犧牲？
The truth is, l wanted this contract--
事實是，我本來是想要那份合同--
And that's how Papa paid you for being attentive to me.
那就是我爸爸付你工錢的方式。
-ln a way, but later-- -Later you got tired of the assignment.
-從某種形式上，但是后來-- -后來你對任務開始厭倦了。
You got in too deep.
你陷得太深了。
So Papa wrote a goodbye note for you to send.
所以爸爸為你寫了一份道別的便條。
l apologize for all the embarrassment this has caused you, Aunt Maria.
Maria阿姨，我為這一切令你難為的事情道歉。
lt was partly my fault.
我也要負一部分責任。
l knew your father was writing the notes.
我是知道你父親寫那些便條的。
Well! Everybody knows now.
哦，大家現在都知道了。
l guess nobody had any way of knowing...
我猜沒有人會想到
...l'd make such a complete fool of myself.
我把自己當傻瓜一樣。
Congratulations, Robert.
祝賀你，Robert.
l hope Papa paid you well. You earned it.
我希望爸爸付給你可人的報酬，那是你自己掙的。
lf l had written the notes...
如果是我寫的那些便條
...l would have meant every word your father said.
我會寫跟你父親一樣的話。
Please, Maria.
別這樣， Maria.
He's working overtime, Papa.
爸爸，他在加班呢。
You should give him a bonus.
你應該給他獎金。
Will you ever forgive me, Maria?
你會原諒我嗎， Maria?
She may, but all my life, l'll be haunted by your frightful suspicions...
可能她會 但是我這輩子都會被你可怕的猜疑心所折磨。
-...that l could have been unfaithful. -Oh, Eduardo!
-...懷疑我的不忠。 -Oh, Eduardo!
Go and see that our guests are happy and leave me with my conscience.
去看看我們的客人是否玩得開心 讓我一個人靜一靜。
-Eduardo-- -Don't say anything.
-Eduardo-- -什么也別說了。
l know, you're a jealous man.
我知道，你是一個忌妒心重的男人。
-Remember, l warned you. -l remember.
-記得嗎，我提醒過你的。 -現在還記得。
My boy, a woman's advice isn't worth listening to...
我的孩子，女人的忠告并不值得仔細聽，
...but any man who doesn't take it is a fool. And that's me.
但是如果你不照做的話就是一個笨蛋 而那個笨蛋就是我。
l've been pretty much of a dope myself.
我覺得我才像個笨蛋。
For some time, it was a positive pleasure...
有些時候，我覺得討厭你
...for me to dislike you.
...是一件很快樂的事情。
lt gave me a nice, warm glow.
就像給我一個溫暖的光亮
But now l must confess that l've conceived quite a fondness for you.
但是現在，我必須承認我挺喜歡你的。
What you just did smacked of nobility.
你剛剛所作的一切，顯示了你高貴的人格。
l didn't want to see you shot full of holes.
我并不想看到你被打成篩子。
Making that confession before Maria, to save me...
為了救我在Maria的面前坦白一切
-...it must have been painful. -lt wasn't any fun.
-..這一定很痛苦。 -這并不快樂。
Do you think she'll be all right now?
你覺得她現在會好些嗎？
Thanks to my meddling, no.
由于我的多管閑事，不會。
l wonder if she'll ever forgive us.
我覺得她永遠也不會原諒我們。
Mr. Acuna, would you mind very much if l didn't take tomorrow's plane?
Acuna先生，你會不會介意如果 我不搭明天那班飛機？
You have my permission to court Maria...
你得到我的許可去追Maria...
...as long as your strength holds out.
...只要你能夠。
But l'm afraid it won't do you any good.
我恐怕這對你沒有任何好處。
lf these orchids aren't out of here by the time l get back, l'll--
等我回來的時候，如果這些蘭花沒有消失，我會---
l'll set fire to them.
我會一把火燒了它們。
Oh, Miss Maria, can't you see how desperate he is?
Oh, Maria小姐, 你難道看不出 他不怕死的決心嗎？
All right. He made love to you under false pretenses...
沒錯，他可能欺騙了你的愛情
...but he's serious now.
...但是他現在是認真的。
You've forgiven me. You can forgive him.
你已經原諒我了，你也能原諒他。
l can't forgive him for what he did to make me love him.
我不能原諒他為了得到我的愛所作的一切。
What about the things you did to make him fall in love with you?
那么你為了得到他的愛所作的一切呢？
When you've got a fish hooked, haul him in.
放下鉤子，把他吊起來。
Don't you let another orchid in this house!
不准讓那些蘭花進到這個屋子里來！
-Miss Maria Acuna. -Right this way, boys.
-給Maria Acuna小姐的. -這邊。
These orchids if you please
這些蘭花給你，如果
With apologies
你可以原諒我。
And another note
還有一張便條
With these Corsage we bring
和這些我們帶的胸花
We're obliged to sing
我們被迫唱
What the sender wrote
這上面寫的話
Quote
引號
Oh, si, si, si, si Mama
Oh, si, si, si, si 媽媽
See how I love you
看看我有多愛你
Oh, si, si, si, si Comma
Oh, si, si, si, si 逗號
Say you love me too
說你也愛我
Now, don't give up, my boy.
別放棄，我的孩子。
You're bucking the man she thought you were.
你這只是回到那個她原以為你是的男人。
-That fellow on the white horse? -Yes.
-你是說，那個騎白馬的家伙？ -對。
-l have an instinct for-- -For what goes on in a woman's heart.
-我有很敏銳的直覺對于 -對于女人在想什么。
-l know. -l know this.
-我知道。 -我知道這個。
Every woman wants to be swept off her feet and carried away.
每個女人都喜歡別人拜倒 在她的裙下然后帶她走。
Tell me, just what did this bird Lochinvar do about his gal?
告訴我，那個Lochinvar對 他的女人做了些什么？
Well, he put on his best suit of Sunday armor...
他穿上他最好的騎士服...
...and rode up to her father's castle, or whatever they lived in.
...然后騎去她父親的城堡 或者其他，他們住的地方。
There was a dance going on, or something...
那里正有一場舞會，或者其他...
...but Lochinvar rode into the patio, or whatever they have in Scotland...
...但是Lochinvar騎馬走進天井 或者其他，不管他們在蘇格蘭有什么
...and swept the girl off her feet, onto his horse and rode off with her.
....跪在那個姑娘的面前 然后騎上馬一起從那里逃走了。
l think.
我這么想。
Well, l've tried everything else.
我已經試過其他所有的方法了。
Robert! Robert!
Robert! Robert!
Wait, Robert!
等等，Robert!
Before we go any further, l've got to get something straight.
在我們再進一步發展之前 有些話我要先說在前面。
This Lochinvar fellow.
這個叫Lochinvar的家伙。
Lochinvar? Never heard of him.
Lochinvar? 從來沒有聽說過。
Darling! That's all l wanted to know.
親愛的！ 我就想知道這個。